icrossing.co.uk 2003-12-08

# 

iCrossing, Inc. (“IC” or “we”) takes your privacy seriously and we want you to understand the ways in which we do and do not use the information that you transmit when you visit our Web sites. This statement discloses the privacy practices for our [www.icrossing.com](http://www.icrossing.com/) and [www.IC-Live.com](http://www.ic-live.com/) sites.

If you feel that iCrossing is not abiding by this privacy policy, please e-mail our Webmaster at [policy@icrossing.com](mailto:policy@icrossing.com).

**Data Collection and Usage**

P3P policies declare the data they collect in groups (also referred to as "statements"). This policy contains 2 data groups. The data practices of each group will be explained separately. 

We collect the following information about our users, which will be used by ourselves and our agents: click-stream data, HTTP protocol elements, search terms, URI of requested resource, query-string portion of URI, request date, request time, other access log fields, user agent information, and navigation and click-stream data. This data will be used for the following purposes: completion and support of the current activity, Web site and system administration, and research and development. 

We use non-personal information such as demographic data to analyze and develop our marketing strategy and to determine how you found out about us, your interests regarding our services and how to further improve our Web site based upon user data. We share non-personal information with our partners and third parties

**Cookies**

Cookies are a technology which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. Our site makes use of cookies. Cookies are used to track visitors to our site so we may better understand what portions of our site best serve you.

Cookies are used by IC for the purposes of user targeting and research and development. Additionally, at the user's option, we will collect HTTP cookies, which will be used for research and development and one-time tailoring. This data will only be used by IC and our agents. 

Our Web server automatically collects some information about you when you request pages from our server, including your IP address. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers connected to the Internet to identify your computer so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you. This information does not identify you personally.

**Log Files**

We also collect IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Web site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personal information. 

**Legal Disclaimer**

We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the requirements of law or comply with legal process served on the Web site.

**Minors**

No portion of our services is directed towards minors (individuals below the age of 18) and we do not knowingly solicit any information about minors or market to minors. 

**Security**

Privacy is very important to iCrossing. We take every precaution to protect our users' information. All information gathered on our [www.icrossing.com](http://www.icrossing.com/) and [www.IC-Live.com](http://www.ic-live.com/) Web sites are protected for storage within a controlled database. However, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. 

If you have any questions about the security of this Web site, please e-mail [policy@icrossing.com](mailto:policy@icrossing.com).

**Notification of Changes**

iCrossing may change this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our site. 

**Business Relationships**

Our Web sites contain links to other Web sites. Please be aware that iCrossing has no control or influence over the privacy practices of such other sites nor is it responsible for the privacy practices or content of such sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave this site and to read the privacy statements of each and every site that collects personal information.

**Enforcement**

If users have any questions or complaints with respect to the principles outlined in this privacy statement or enforcement of this privacy statement they should contact:

iCrossing, Inc.  
15721 North Greenway-Hayden Loop  
Scottsdale, AZ 85260 USA
